jumbomail.me 2019-05-21

# JumboMail Privacy policy

JumboMail takes the privacy of its users very seriously. If at any time data is collected when using our products and services, you will be informed instantly. Data is used by JumboMail only for aiding improvements to the site and will not be passed onto third parties.  
JumboMail takes every possible reasonable measure to prevent illegal entry into the site and unauthorized information/files from being stored. JumboMail will not pass on or provide your personal data to a third party unless obliged to do so by a court order. JumboMail will use information about users behavior patterns on the site in order to make improvements to the services, operation and customer interaction.

Some services on JumboMail require users to register. During the registration process, users will be required to provide personal information such as name, address, contact information, e-mail or credit card details. Fields which must be completion shall be stated. Without providing the necessary data in the mandatory fields, users will not be eligible to register for additional services. Throughout the registration process, users will only be requested to provide general information. Only while purchasing JumboCodes or subscription to JumboMail services, users are prompted to provide credit cards details among other information. Anyway, credit card details are not stored on the JumboMail servers and when you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

Like many web sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes.  
For example, to make your next visit easier, JumboMail installs a cookie that remembers your user ID. JumboMail furthermore stores your IP-address, country and language settings, browser type and Flash version. JumboMail stores this data for a maximum of 12 months/1 year, where after it is automatically deleted.  
Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser. JumboMail does not have access to or control of any cookies that its advertisers may store in your browser and this Privacy Policy does not apply to the use of cookies by advertisers.  
You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the web sites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all the functionality of the Services

If you wish to remove all the cookies that jumbomail uses, click on "remove cookies" button.

Delete Cookies

JumboMail takes your trust and privacy very seriously and therefore aims to process as little personal data as necessary. You therefore do not have to sign up for an account, nor is there any other kind of log-in procedure obligation for using the free services. In order to use our service and send your file(s), it is indispensable to enter your own email address, add the file(s) you wish to transfer and the email addresses of the recipients. You might also add a personal message for the recipients along with your File. To enable you to use our service, JumboMail needs to process this data when sending a file(s). We will principally use your personal data only for sending your file and improving our service. We surely won’t sell it to third or affiliate parties or use it for irritating commercial messages.

You are only allowed to use our Website and/or Service when of or over the age of 16 years, or with the approval of your parents or guardians.

If you have questions about the way JumboMail processes your personal data or the personal information JumboMail stores about you, please contact JumboMail by sending an email with your question to [support@jumbomail.me](mailto:support@jumbomail.me). We speak English.

Jumbomail Technologies Ltd  reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time.
